sup everyone so here I am I decided to
read the first comic of my sock on comic
book series soccer on episode 1 the
journey begins fell during the team now
I have no idea what's in it but whatever
it is God be and the cover
is cool Sonic is in it Manic ‘ns in it
Sonia is in it all the kicks every loves
no one thing I gotta say right away that
kind of even got her mind of the bed is
Sonia and every single sentence with the
wood yo that's right all I like that i
like what is it y'all this place isn't
creepy yo now in case I've got any kids
following me on you child you may not
know the wood yo was a it was something
all the cool kids said in the early two
thousands and to be honest I was only a
cool kid I wanted to be a cool kid but I
wasn't that like at school I get in line
school people with bullying me and
for locking sock on the ground or some
yeah it's kind of stupid but I
guess I guess I am I guess I am a cod
unlike them I ended up the cool kid i
mean I do own a youtube channel they
don't they most likely dogs I don't know
I actually give a Benny that's the
reason Sonia says yo because because in
other times it was cool I made these in
the over 2,000 that's all like that's
all I will have to say about that
you know I'm going off off let's free
that's wrong are you sure it's safe to
be in the Mobius for Sonja this place is
creepy this place isn't creepy yo and no
it isn't safe yo that's the reason we're
here you know we finally still it a
living tree that attacked me up scary so
far that touch me what happened
ah I'll living tree oh that you happy
it's funny Sonia Sonic song you look at
that what is it yo he's playing charades
I guess he's a bit oh oh that's funny
vicious some ow he's not playing he's
choking y'all what are we I'm coming
Manic oh yeah oh don't know why she
said that look at that everyone else go
he draw the keyboard but I didn't hear
Sonic bro how thanks a lot Sonic no prom
attic let's go yo
ah that's Dingo yo oh no you feldene
face it's sleek to at least a nice we
got two of them Dingo well you can save
the day now now you may not be
warning although I do the same for
selling it I do for fell he ends every
single sentence off with the phrase my
boy cuz you don't know that because he
calls matting my boy in EM so one and I
guess I just kept it as a running gag
for some reason stupid but yeah that's
just it it's the overgrown stink
bug yo how unexpected so let him go my
boy yo yo she's shooting a basket you
don't know this all babies intensive
spot look at that ah yeah you won't get
this one no Manik you miss stupid ah you
made us knows I'm sorry slate or Treat
Dingo at least Robotnik won't tell her
heads we got we have the green Hedgehog
the with Manic is he then I don't
know
thank God Manic Wow Oh No so what dad so
he is a bitchiness Max not gamma boy
he's with us you mean up there no he's
here yeah I'm eric mel save me you're my
boy son you notice something and oh
like that huh two big continued ends up
a cliffhanger damn common friend
subscribe let me know if you want me to
upper part 2 I’ve got God I've gone with
you under these comics let me know if I
should even do them up oh I'm just
wasting my time with this
Oh